apkios.net 2017-11-05

# Privacy Policy - Apkios.net

**This privacy document was last revised on February 13, 2017.**

At Apkios, your privacy is our number one concern. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information being received and collected by apkios.net (The Site) and how it is used.

**Personal Information**

apkios.net does not require any information which can be traced back to, and identify a unique user. Certain features of the site however (like comments for example) , do require a valid email address to verify legitimate users. We guarantee that the information provided to The Site would never be used for any other purpose.

**Log Files**

Like many other web sites, Apkios makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. All of the data recorded is not linked to any information that could personally identify a unique individual.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This site itself, does not use any cookies to store information. Third party service providers however may store information on your computer. Refer to the following sections to understand what information is collected and how to opt out of the process.  
DISQUS Comments:  
Apkios uses Disqus Comments system to collect and manage comments on the site. Disqus, as a third party service provider uses cookies to maintain your Disqus profile. You may easily opt out of the process by not posting a comment on the site.

**External Sites**

Apkios may often link to content on external websites. The Site has no control over the nature of content on these external websites or their policies regarding information and privacy. For further information, please review the individual policies of these websites.

**Third party advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of some of these third party advertising companies and learn which of these companies allow you to opt-out of this type of information collection, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Policy Changes**

Apkios.net reserves the right to make any (major or minor) change to this privacy document without any prior warning. The site may or may not notify the users regarding any change made to the policy, however we will always reflect the latest policies and their effective dates in this document.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [website’s privacy policy.](https://apkios.net/privacy-policy/)

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using :  rlsper99 @ gmail.com
